liveforfilms.com 2018-11-26

# Privacy Policy | Live for Films

We Respect Your Privacy.

We are committed to protecting the personal data that we hold and use about you and to respecting your privacy.

This privacy notice describes the data that we collect from you or about you, and the way that we use it. Please read the privacy notice carefully as it will help you to understand the way that we use your personal data and our reasons for doing so.

**What personal data do we collect?**

This privacy notice gives you information about the way that we use your “personal data”. Personal data is any information that could be used to identify you in some way (even if, in some scenarios such as online advertising, we don’t know your name). The personal data that we collect from or about you will include the following:

_name;_  
_name of the organisation, society or entity that you represent;_  
_business/organisation address;_  
_business/organisation e-mail address; and_  
_business/organisation or personal phone number._

In connection with services that we provide to you or procure from you, we will also collect information related to those services. For example:

  * if you are a journalist, we may collect contact details so we can keep in touch to arrange screenings, review copies to be sent out
  * if you are a business partner, we may collect contact information to keep you up to date on any work we are doing with you

**How do we collect personal data?**

We may collect personal data directly from you:

Information such as your preferred means of communication and information about services that you request or provide may be collected when you voluntarily provide this information to us; and  
In some cases, it will be mandatory for you to provide this information in order for us to meaningfully be able to respond to your query or provide the information or service that you have requested. For example if you are a competition winner we would need your postal address. This would only be passed to the company provided the prize so they could arrange delivery.

**How do we share your personal data?**

We will never sell your personal data or give it to anyone else for them to use for their own purposes without making that clear to you and obtaining your consent where necessary.

**Security and retention of your personal data**

(i) Security of your personal data:

We take the security of your personal data very seriously. We have implemented various strategies, controls and measures to keep your data secure and we keep these measures under close review in line with legal and technological developments.

(ii) Retention of your personal data:

In broad terms, we will only retain your personal data for as long as is necessary for the purposes described in this privacy notice.

**Your rights and how to contact us**

Applicable data protection laws give you a number of rights in relation to your personal data and our use of it. You have the right:

(A) to ask us not to use your personal data for direct marketing purposes;  
(B) to ask to see what personal data we hold about you and to find out about the way that we process your personal data (and in some circumstances, you can ask us to provide a copy to a third party);  
(C) to ask us to correct or update any personal data which is inaccurate;  
(D) to ask for personal data to be deleted in some (but not all) circumstances where there is no good reason for us to continue to use it;  
(E) to ask us to temporarily stop using your personal data if you don’t believe that we have a right to use it, or to stop us from using your personal data where there is no good reason for us to continue to use it; and  
If you would like to exercise any of the rights listed above, or if you have any queries or concerns about the way that we use your personal data (or any questions about this privacy notice), you can contact us at liveforfilms@outlook.com

**Changes to our privacy notice**

Any changes we may make to our privacy notice in the future will be posted on this page (if applicable).
